{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "12/20/2015",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "12/12/2022",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "12/20/2015",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "12/12/2022",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2024",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 1974",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/19/2017",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "12/12/2022",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "12/12/2021",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on December 20, 2020. The Patriots won the game 22-12.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 25, 2018.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 25, 2018.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 25, 2018.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 21, 2021.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 20, 2024",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 23, 2024",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2024",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019. The Patriots lost to the Dolphins 27-20.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019. The Patriots lost 27-20.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019. The Patriots lost 27-20.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2013.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 7,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2013",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2013",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "11/24/2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The last time the Patriots played the Dolphins was on November 24, 2019. The Patriots won the game 27-20.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2013.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019, the Patriots defeated the Dolphins 43-0.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 6,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Patriots last played the Dolphins on November 24, 2019.",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 10,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "November 24, 2019",
            "needle": "The Patriots last played the Miami Dolphins on November 24, 2024.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "On what date did the Patriots last play the Miami Dolphins?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}